The Tower of the Moon
This tower is a giant cannon that aims at the human server on the moon
At this rate, the remaining data of humanity will be destroyed
Hahaha... It doesn't matter... It doesn't matter anymore...
Did you know? We don't need this world
Humanity is already destroyed
The Moon's disguised server was created to make Android fight
The Yorha unit was prepared to protect that lie
It was planned to be destroyed from the beginning for the destruction of evidence
The backdoor set up by the bunker was activated at a certain time
The commander, me, and 2B...
Everything was a waste
It's funny, isn't it? It's funny, isn't it?
9S... We...
You killed 2B, didn't you?
That's enough
The reason we kill each other...
2B was suffering
You...
To keep killing
9S type of high-performance model was expected to reach the truth
Her model name 2B is a fake
The real name of the model is...
The official name is...
2E...
2E type of high-performance model
The unit was prepared to execute the Yorha unit
You've already noticed, haven't you?
9S...
Shut up...
Shut up!
What do you know about us?
The command "Stop the battle. Do not speak to her here."
I command POD No.1!
Do not speak or think about your own logic!
This command is...
Hold it until I can confirm the stop of either A2 or my life activities!
I will not let you die!
Hehe...
I don't care anymore, Tenbu!
9S!
But...
Why do I miss humans so much?
Why do I want to touch humans even though they're gone?
That's because they're made!
We androids are made to protect humanity!
That basic program is our heart!
Shut up! Shut up! Shut up!
I just have to...
I just have to lose everything!
Damn!
9S...
Please...
Tenbu...
What?
I'm sorry...