[Music]
The body that can catch the disappearing scoop
The sky is still dark
The stopped clock is a machine that doesn't ring
My voice can't reach
This is my curse
The depth of the sin I committed
Your wish
My defiled soul
I don't know what to do
Yes, we are now
Screaming at that value
The song of that broken world
Yes, we are now
I wish in that sense
Just the future with you
The smile of that day
Disappeared with love
[Music]
The green overflows
The life spills
The wind is still far away
The rust that peels off
The blade that grumbles
In the forest where the dead are hidden
This is my curse
The pain of killing promises
Your wish
I threw away my last dream
It's not good, but
Yes, we are now
Screaming at that value
The love of this dirty world
Yes, we are now
I wish in that sense
Just the time with you
The consciousness that fell
Disappeared with kindness
[Music]
Yes, we are now
Screaming at that value
The song of that broken world
Yes, we are now
I wish in that sense
Just the future with you
Yes, we are now
Screaming at that value
The love of this dirty world
Yes, we are now
I wish in that sense
Just the time with you
Even if prayer cannot be forgiven
[Music]
I am